Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1991
    - Cooper Union, October-December 1991
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), 1991-10-25, AFC 2014/044: EMCS 91-1025_3; Note on media: Son de la Loma
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), 1991-11-21, AFC 2014/044: EMCS 91-1121_5; Note on media: NY Buenos Aires
        - 1 sound disc (CD), 1991-10-25, EMCS 91-1025; Note on media: Cooper Union Fall Series: Son de la Loma y Los Pleneros de la 21 (Box 16)
        - 9 audio files (wav): digital., 1991-10-25, EMCS911025
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1991-10-25, EMCS_91-1025-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1991-11-21, EMCS_91-1121-5
    - First Fridays, December 1991
      - Sound Recordings, 1991-12-06
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS/FF 91-1206_1; Note on media: Mbira/Shekere Sound Experience
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS/FF 91-1206_2; Note on media: African Express
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., EMCS-FF_91-1206-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., EMCS-FF_91-1206-2
    - Other events, 1991
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1991, Note on folder: First Fridays (Box-folder 5/29)
        - 1 folder, 1991, Note on folder: New-York Historical Society (Box-folder 5/30)
        - 1 folder, 1991-02, Note on folder: Why History? Race and Class in New York City (Box-folder 5/32)
        - 1 folder, 1991-02-06, Note on folder: First Fridays: Norwegian (Box-folder 6/11)
        - 1 folder, 1991-12-19, Note on folder: Worlds of Folk Arts (ARAP Conference) (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1991, CCI 91; Note on folder: Casa do Minho - Newark, NJ (Box-folder 12/1)
        - 1 folder, 1991-09-29, CCI 91-0929; Note on folder: Klezmer Orchestra (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), 1991-03-27, AFC 2014/044: EMCS 91-0327_01; Note on media: Why History: Bridging the Gap
      - Sound Recordings
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., 1991-04-01, EMCS-FF_91_0401_4
  - Events, 1992
    - Second Annual Albanian Festival, October 1992
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1992-10-18
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Moving Images, 1992-10-18
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_01; Note on media: Master tape 1 of 3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_02; Note on media: Master Tape 2 of 3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_03; Note on media: Master Tape 3 of 3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_04; Note on media: Reel 1A
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_05; Note on media: Reel 2A
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_06; Note on media: Reel 3A
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_07; Note on media: Hi-8 transfer
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_08; Note on media: Studio Viktoria 1
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_09; Note on media: Studio Viktoria 2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_10; Note on media: Studio Viktoria 3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_11; Note on media: Studio Viktoria 4
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_12; Note on media: EFAC 3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_13; Note on media: EFAC 4
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_14; Note on media: EFAC 5
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_15; Note on media: Sampler
      - Sound Recordings, 1992-10-18
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_1
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 92-1018_2
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 92-1018-1 (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 92-1018-2 (Box 15)
        - 53 audio files (wav): digital., CCI-92-1018-1
        - 28 audio files (wav): digital., CCI_92_1018_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_92-1018-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI-92-1018-2
    - Sister Sadie and the Famous Biblettes and the Heavenly Tones, March-October 1992
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1992-03-15 (Box-folder 6/13)
        - 1 folder, 1992-05-02 (Box-folder 6/18)
        - 1 folder, 1992-10-24 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1992-10-24, EMCS-NYHS_92-1024-1
    - Other events, 1992
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1992, Note on folder: Middlesex County Cultural and Heritage Com. FY '92 Series (Box-folder 6/10)
        - 1 folder, 1992, Note on folder: New-York Historical Society (Box-folder 6/20)
        - 1 folder, 1992-02-15, Note on folder: Calabria Bella and the DeFranco Family with Francesco Cofone (Box-folder 6/12)
        - 1 folder, 1992-04-03, Note on folder: Green Music: An Evening of Irish Traditional Music & Dance (Box-folder 6/14)
        - 1 folder, 1992-04-04, Note on folder: Music from Appalachia (Box-folder 6/15)
        - 1 folder, 1992-04-11, Note on folder: Argentinean Tango - The NY-Buenos Aires Connection (Box-folder 6/16)
        - 1 folder, 1992-04-26, Note on folder: Festa Convivo (Box-folder 6/17)
        - 1 folder, 1992-05-09, Note on folder: Klezmer Music: Brave New World (Box-folder 6/19)
        - 1 folder, 1992-11-22 (Box-folder 6/23)
        - 1 folder, 1992-1993, Note on folder: Shashmaqam Tour (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1992-04-26, CCI 92-0426; Note on folder: Portugese Rancho DeFranco Rehearsal - Elizabeth, NJ (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1992-11-07, ECMS-NYHS_92-1107-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1992-11-07, ECMS-NYHS_92-1107-2
  - Events, 1993
    - Prospect Park Concert, May 1993
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1993-05-22
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Moving Images, 1993-05-22
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_01; Note on media: Tango A-1; NY Buenos Aires Connection
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_02; Note on media: Tango A-2; NY Buenos Aires Connection
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_03; Note on media: Tango B-1; NY Buenos Aires Connection
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_04; Note on media: Tango B-2; NY Buenos Aires Connection
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_05; Note on media: Pablo /Raul intervierw
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_01-02; Note on media: Tango
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_05; Note on media: Tango: Interview: Pablo Raul
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_10; Note on media: Tango A1-2 window dub
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_11; Note on media: Tango B1-2 window dub
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522A_12; Note on media: Pablo Raul Interview
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_01; Note on media: A-1; Los Pleneros de la 21
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_02; Note on media: A-2; Los Pleneros de la 21
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_03; Note on media: B-1; Los Pleneros de la 21
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_04; Note on media: B-2; Los Pleneros de la 21
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_1-2; Note on media: Tango, NY Buenos Aires Connection B 1-2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_05; Note on media: Les Plameros A 1-2, Audio TK #1 TC Performance
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_06; Note on media: Los Pameros
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_07; Note on media: Plameros de la 21C, EFAC Prospect Park. Picnic House
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_08; Note on media: Plameros. A1,2 window dub
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522B_09; Note on media: Plameros B1,2 window dub
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C; Note on media: EFAC 5-22-93 Tango, NY Buenos Aires Connection C
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_01; Note on media: A-1; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_02; Note on media: A-2; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_03; Note on media: A-3; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_04; Note on media: B-1; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_05; Note on media: B-2; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_1-5; Note on media: A-1, A-2, A-3 (Shashmaqam); B-1, B-2
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam SP, 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_06; Note on media: B-3; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_07; Note on media: Shashmagam A1-2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_08; Note on media: Shashmagam A3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_09; Note on media: Shashmagam B1
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_10; Note on media: Shashmagam B2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_11; Note on media: Shashmagam B3
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_12; Note on media: Shashmagam C
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_13; Note on media: Shashmagam C2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_14; Note on media: Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_15; Note on media: Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C_16; Note on media: Shashmagam B2-3
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 93-0522C, 93-0522B_01-04; Note on media: Greek Concert and Dance Party
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 93-0522c_0522b1-4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 93-0522c_0522b1-4
    - Folk Parks: Brooklyn Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, September 1993
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1993-09-26
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 6/30)
      - Photographs, 1993-09-26
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 12/2)
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Moving Images, 1993-09-26
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_02
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_04
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_05
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_06
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_07
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_08
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_09
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_10
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_11
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 93-0926_12
    - Other events, 1993
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1993, Note on folder: Rhythms of New York (Why History?) (Box-folder 6/25)
        - 1 folder, 1993-04-25, Note on folder: Portugese Traditional Music and Dance (Box-folder 6/26)
        - 1 folder, 1993-05-23, Note on folder: "Song Bring Us Together" A Concert of Albanian Music and Dance (Box-folder 6/28)
        - 1 folder, 1993-06-13, Note on folder: Jazz Des Jeunes in Prospect Park (Box-folder 6/29)
        - 1 folder, 1993-10-31, Note on folder: Thrid Annual Albanian Festival (Box-folder 6/31)
        - 1 folder, 1993-12-05, Note on folder: The Brooklyn Museum - Near Eastern Music Ensemble (Box-folder 6/32)
        - 1 folder, 1993-1994, Note on folder: Shashmaqam Tour (Box-folder 6/33)
  - Events, 1994
    - Riverbank festival / NY Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, May 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1994-05-30
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Moving Images, 1994-05-30
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-0530_03; Note on media: Los Pleneros / Antillies / Inkhay
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-0530_04; Note on media: Los Pleneros / Antillies / Inkhay
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-0530_05; Note on media: Spirit Ensemble / Jose Quesada
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-0530_06; Note on media: Jose Quesada / Inkhay
    - Mahrajan al-Fan (1st Festival of Arab World Culture), September 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1994-09-11
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Moving Images, 1994-09-11
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 94-0911_4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 94-0911_dvcam1
    - Folk Parks '94: Second Annual Brooklyn Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, October 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1994-10-23
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/8)
        - 1 oversize folder (Container oversize folder 1)
      - Sound Recordings, 1994-10-23
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 94-1023-3; Note on media: Besim Muriqi and Ramiz Islami Orchestra (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 94-1023-5; Note on media: De Franco Family (Box 16)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_6; Note on media: Mariachi Xochimilco
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_7; Note on media: Besim Muriqi
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_8; Note on media: The Great Day Chorale
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_9; Note on media: V.R.A.N.A. Cultural Troupe
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_10; Note on media: Ramiz Islami Orchestra, Prospect Park
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 94-1023_11; Note on media: Los Majaderos
        - 22 audio files (wav): digital., FP94-1023
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., FP94-1023-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-6
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-7
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-8
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-9
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-10
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-11
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_94-1023-12
    - Fourth Annual Albanian Festival, October 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1994-10-30
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Sound Recordings, 1994-10-30
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 94-1030_3; Note on media: Lehman Center for the Performing Arts, Bronx, NY
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 94-1030_4
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 94-1030_5
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 94-1030-3 (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 94-1030-4 (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 94-1030-5 (Box 15)
        - 37 audio files (wav): digital., CCI-94-1030-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_94-1030-3
        - 61 audio file (wav): digital., CCI-94-1030-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_94-1030-4
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., CCI-94-1030-5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_94-1030-5
    - Winter Lights Concert Series: Hasidic Klezmer Music, December 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1994-12-27
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Photographs, 1994-12-30
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Sound Recordings, 1994-12-27
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS/WL 94-1227_1; Note on media: Andy Statman Trio; Andrea Hoag and Paul Morrissett
        - 2 sound discs (CD), EMCS/WL 94-1227-1; Note on media: Andy Statman (Box 16)
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS-WL_94_1227_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., EMCS-WL_94-1227-1
    - Other events, 1994
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1994, Note on folder: BACA Folk Arts '94 (Box-folder 6/34)
        - 1 folder, 1994, Note on folder: Crown Heights History Project (Box-folder 6/35)
        - 1 folder, 1994, Note on folder: Musical Traditions of Crown Heights (Box-folder 6/36)
        - 1 folder, 1994-02-12, Note on folder: Brave Old World (Box-folder 6/37)
        - 1 folder, 1994-03-05, Note on folder: Music from China (Box-folder 7/1)
        - 1 folder, 1994-03-06, Note on folder: Near Eastern Music Ensemble (Box-folder 7/2)
        - 1 folder, 1994-04-10, Note on folder: Cherish the Ladies (Box-folder 7/3)
        - 1 folder, 1994-05-10, Note on folder: Brave Old World (Box-folder 7/4)
        - 1 folder, 1994-05-21, Note on folder: Conjunto Melodia Tropical (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1994, CCI 94; Note on folder: Palestinian Gathering (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), 1994-04-23, AFC 2014/044: TOUR/SHASH 94-0423_1-3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 1994-04-23, Tour/Shash 94-0423-1-3
  - Events, 1995
    - Winter Lights Concert Series: Music from China and Los Pleneros de la 21, January 1995
      - Sound Recordings, 1995-01-01 to 1995-01-05
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS/WL 95-0104_1; Note on media: Los Pleneros de la 21 (January 4); Music from China (January 5; first set)
        - 2 sound discs (CD), EMCS/WL 95-0101-1; Note on media: Master Recording Source: DAT Tape (Box 16)
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS-WL_95_0104_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., EMCS-WL_95-0104-1
    - Jaliya Kafo, Museum of African Art, April 1995
      - Sound Recordings, 1995-04-15
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 95-0415_1
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 95-0415-1; Note on media: Master Recording Source: DAT Master (Box 15)
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_95-0415-1
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., CCI_95_0415_1
    - Folk Parks '95 New York Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, May-June 1995
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1995
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/12)
        - 1 oversize folder (Container oversize folder 1)
      - Photographs, 1995-05-29
        - 1 folder, FP 95-0529; Note on folder: Poongmul Nori - Folk Parks, Riverbank (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Photographs, 1995-06-11
        - 1 folder, FP 95-0611; Note on folder: Folk Parks, Van Cortlandt (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Sound Recordings, 1995-05-29
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0529_1; Note on media: Renacer Trovero; Deep in da Circle, Seamus Egan
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0529_2; Note on media: El Popular Agua y Su Explosion Tipica Dominicana
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0529_3; Note on media: William Cepeda (Puerto Rican bomba and plena)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0529_4; Note on media: Andy Statman; William Cepeda
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0529_5; Note on media: Roy Campbell and 'Tazz
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0529-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0529-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0529-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0529-5
      - Sound Recordings, 1995-06-11
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_3; Note on media: Bronx: Yuri Yunakov (continued); Jose Quezada
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_4; Note on media: Bronx: Mi Tierra Natal; The Four Winds
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_5; Note on media: Bronx: Klezmer (continued); Beyle Gottesman with David Krakauer
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 95-0611-3b; Note on media: Bronx: Jose Quezada and Los Cinco Diablos (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 95-0611-6; Note on media: Bronx: Kabajo: West African (Ghanaian) Highlife (Box 16)
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0611-1
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., FP95-0611-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0611-3
        - 12 audio files (wav): digital., FP95-0611-FP95-0611-3b
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0611-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_95-0611-5
      - Moving Images, 1995-06-11
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_01; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_02; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_03; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_04; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_05; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 95-0611_06; Note on media: Venue: Van Cortlandt park
    - Mahrajan al-Fan: A Two-Day Festival of Arab World Culture (2nd Annual), 1995-1998
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1995-09-16; 1998-05-07 (Box-folder 7/11)
        - 1 oversize folder, 1995-09-16 to 1995-09-17 (Container oversize folder 1)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), 1995-09-16; 1998-05-07, AFC 2014/044: CCI 95-0916_1, 98-0507_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 1995-09-16 to 1995-09-17, CCI 95-0916-0917
    - Taking Root: Songs of the Greek Diaspora and the Homeland, December 1995
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1995-12-02
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Sound Recordings, 1995-12-02
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 95-1202_1; Note on media: Greek concert: Greenwich House, New York City
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 95-1202-1; Note on media: Aman Amerika Orchestra, Jim Jarras, Grigoris Maninakis, Anna Paidousi (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 95-1202-1; Note on media: Aman Amerika Orchestra, Jim Karras, Grigoris Maninakis, Anna Paidousi (Box 15)
        - 35 audio files (wav): digital., CCI-95-1202-1
        - 17 audio files (wav): digital., CCI_95_1202_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_95-1202-1
    - Other events, 1995
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1995-10-29
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Events, 1996
    - Music of China, University Settlement House, April 1996
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1996-04-14
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Sound Recordings, 1996-04-14
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 96-0414_1